[Music]
so while many plans in the market offers
multiple claims for critical units
the odds of a customer making multiple
claim is low especially for late stage
critical illnesses this may mean that a
customer is paying more for coverage
that they may not utilize
so fwd recover first offers a good
balance in this aspect as it allows one
to make a claim for late stage illnesses
even after a claim for early critical
units while keeping the prices
reasonable
[Music]
i have this client with congenital heart
issue born with a hole in the heart i
met him last year for financial planning
and he was concerned about his critical
illness coverage health wise he is in
his 20s young and healthy having said
that the client faced rejection and
exclusions from other insurers however
fwd studied this case and after careful
consideration of the application with
declarations and reports provided the
client was able to get 100 coverage from
fwd recover first the whole process
really illustrated to me how fwd is an
insurer that truly cares and changes the
way people feel about insurance
[Music]
you